Good morning. Did y'all hear?
Man, they're making some changes to the Small Doses podcast.
Changes? We just added video.
I know about that.
This is triggering my abandonment issues.
You know, Small Doses, ever since they added video, you've changed.
Only in the best ways.
You have maintenance. You need an editor, a camera, a producer.
Y'all know what I'm saying.
I mean, see me, I just get on stage with a mic and I do my thing.
I mean, well, I'm a whole independently produced political comedy documentary, but who's voting?
It's true. It's true.
Well, apparently Amanda's Pockets voted and they said that they can no longer give away all our videos for free.
So that's it?
I mean, I bought a whole pink wardrobe.
There's a pink couch. We made a whole pink room.
It's like every week we have insightful conversations nestled in a womb.
Ooh, I have so many punchlines right now.
Relax. She's not ditching Small Doses videos altogether.
You just got to be a member of Patreon to get them.
You mean like how you can only see me on Netflix and other streaming services?
No, Blondie.
It's fine.
Yeah, except instead of giving your money to HBO...
It's Max now.
Never.
You giving it straight to Amanda?
Okay, okay.
Well, I think that's fair.
You know, the audio is pro bono, but this face is worth a million bucks.
Extra. See? Extra.
See you on Patreon.
Derek!
Smile, don't say.
And even if you're real, smile, don't say.